What the...
Are you kidding me?
Just bring me back to life already.
I'm pretty sure I was...
on my way to go skiing with my coworkers.
So did our bus get into an accident?
But my memories are...
Are all the people standing
in this line... dead?
Chief Igarashi...
I will now begin guiding
you all in order.
Please proceed forward calmly.
She's here, too?
Next, please.
Mr. Arihito Atobe?
Uh, yes?
Please take this.
Once you arrive,
go to the guild first
and choose your job.
Guild?
Well, then...
Welcome to Labyrinth Country!
Huh?
THE WORLD'S STRONGEST REARGUARD
A NOVICE SEEKER IN LABYRINTH COUNTRY
So this is the guild?
Well, I came here like
she told me to, so...
That lady...
I think she was on the bus with me.
Ms. Suzuna Shiromiya, thank you
for filling out the paperwork.
I see the job you're hoping
for is Shrine Maiden.
Congratulations!
I've assessed your aptitude,
and your request was accepted.
Hey, got a minute?
Uh, y-yes... Can I help you?
I'm new in this town...
I know. Anyone who's
registering at this guild
is a novice who just reincarnated here.
I'm looking for someone
with a rearguard job.
There's a part of my vanguard
job that's... not the best.
It might not be easy for a novice
like you to team up with me...
Check it out. Elitia's trying
to recruit people again.
B-But if you join a party,
you should level up quickly.
Wonder how many days this one'll last.
So please form a party with me!
Huh?
No matter how strong she is,
as long as she has that, it's
always gonna end the same way.
What does that mean?
Thank you for inviting me.
S-So you'll do it?
Thanks!
Okay, first of all, let's go
get some tea or something!
Sir...
You have an unregistered license?
Oh... Yes.
Then please step right up.
I'll take care of
your Seeker registration
and provide any advice you may need.
My name is Louisa Farmel.
Here in Labyrinth Country, only
those who register as Seekers
are permitted to enter labyrinths.
For starters, please
present your license.
Um... before that, can you tell me...
What is "Labyrinth Country," exactly?
Labyrinth Country is a nation
that is home only to Seekers,
who explore labyrinths, and
those who support them.
People whose souls reincarnate
into Labyrinth Country
begin new lives here as Seekers.
Reincarnate? Seeker?
Yeah, I guess I really
did die back there.
S-Sir?
Your memories are in disarray because
you only just reincarnated.
I'm sorry I explained things in
such depth right off the bat.
Would you like to be seen by a Healer?
Oh... No, I'm all right.
It was just a bit of a headache.
So, um... the first thing I
need to do is register, right?
You'll find that the "Job" line
on your license is blank.
Please write the job you think
you are most suited for,
or the one you most want
to try, in that blank.
So I'm not choosing from
a specific set of jobs?
People reincarnate here with all
sorts of different backgrounds.
This system allows us to
make the most of that.
Whether or not I'm able to get
a job that's in high demand
will determine whether I get off
to a good start or a bad one.
Please take all the time
you need to think it over.
A job, huh?
Atobe-kun! I have an idea
for a really cool project!
ATOBE-KUN!
Give me any thoughts you may have!
I'll use 'em all!
Before I reincarnated, I was
worked to the bone every day
LET'S GO!!
ATOBE-KUN
by an elite boss who was younger
than me. Work was hell.
But now I'm in Labyrinth
Country, a different world.
I won't have to work under a
high-powered career woman,
and I'm free from the
shackles of that company.
For now, I just want to set myself
up for a nice, easy life.
Atobe-kun!
Gah! Chief Igarashi!
What do you mean, "gah"?
Oh, sorry... I guess, since you're
here, you must've also...
Yeah. I died back home
and reincarnated here.
Everything I see here makes me think
this is some cosplay world...
but we'll be starting our
new lives here, huh?
Though it hasn't really hit me yet that
I'll have to fight monsters and stuff.
What? Monsters?!
That's one of the things people
who reincarnate here do for work.
Here, your job and who you party up
with are matters of life and death.
Yes, I guess so.
Atobe-kun, have you not
picked your job yet?
If you could get one that gives me
someone to turn to, that'd be great.
Um... incidentally, Chief,
what job did you pick?
Me? I'm...
Actually...
we're not boss and
subordinate anymore, so...
Instead of "Chief"...
N-Nothing! Never mind!
My job is Valkyrie.
I can use swords and spears,
and apparently, I'll be able
to use some spirit magic.
That sounds like a pretty impressive job.
I figure I'll have a better chance at
surviving if I can do lots of things.
The most crucial point of a party is
how roles within it are divided up,
so you want to avoid having multiple
people with the same job.
I see. Thank you for the lesson.
Then I should choose something that'll
make me useful to my partymates.
Your partymates?
Huh? Oh, er, I mean...
I-If we both manage to survive,
let's meet up again somewhere,
Chief Igarashi.
Got it! I should hurry up and find
some partymates myself, then!
She didn't seem like her usual self...
Hey, I'm sure she'll be fine.
Well? Have you decided?
Oh, um...
In that case, I'll explain
a bit more about jobs.
A Seeker's job directly affects
their Contribution Points.
Contribution Points?
Bringing back rare treasures,
defeating strong monsters,
saving a companion's life...
Performing such actions in labyrinths
will earn you Contribution Points.
And...
the number of points you have determines
your place in the Seeker hierarchy.
SEEKING RESULTS
Your activities in labyrinths are
recorded and displayed on this page.
NO RESULTS TO DISPLAY YET
Wow, it's almost like a tablet.
The hierarchy determines your
status in Labyrinth Country,
the food, shelter, and clothing you
get, and various other things.
People at the bottom sometimes
have to live in stables.
I'd rather avoid that...
Um, Louisa-san...
Are rearguard jobs in high
demand, even for novices?
Yes, a rearguard is
essential to any party,
but they have lower stamina and defense
than vanguard and midguard jobs,
so they're less likely to still
be around in five years.
That means there's always a
demand for rearguard jobs.
If they're in demand, it might be worth
choosing one, despite the risks.
What rearguard job would I be good in?
Maybe if I just put "Rearguard,"
it'll automatically pick the
one I'm most cut out for...
REARGUARD
Huh?
Let me just take a quick look at this...
What in the world did you write?
"Rearguard."
Congratulations, Mr. Atobe!
Your request has been accepted!
Uh, h-hang on a minute, Louisa-san!
Just... what job did I end up getting?
Y-You're a Rearguard.
At least... I think you're a Rearguard.
SWORDSMAN
To be honest, I've never
seen this language before.
Normally, whatever a Seeker
writes stays as it was written.
But when it's a job that
has no precedent, well...
I know I told you it was
always in demand, but...
You might find it difficult
to form a party.
I consider myself partly responsible
for giving you that advice,
so I'll enact special measures.
Until you figure out
your job's strengths,
please use these Mercenary Tickets.
DEFENSE SUPPORT LV. 1: REDUCES INJURY
TO PARTY MEMBERS IN FRONT BY 10 POINTS
So the skills I can acquire are...
ATTACK SUPPORT LV. 1:
ADDS 10 INJURY POINTS TO ATTACKS
BY PARTY MEMBERS IN FRONT
SUPPORT RECOVERY LV. 1:
RESTORES 5 VITALITY POINTS EVERY
30 SECONDS TO PARTY MEMBERS IN FRONT
REAR VIEW: SPENDS 5 MAGIC POINTS
TO EXPAND YOUR VISION TO COVER YOUR
REAR FOR A SET PERIOD OF TIME
How much is ten points of damage, anyway?
I guess "Rear View" allows a rearguard
with low stamina to watch the rear.
That sounds useful, too,
but the one I should take first
is is Defense Support 1,
and after testing that out, Support
Recovery 1, so I can heal...
No, I'll put that one on hold.
I'll find out if there are potions
or other ways to heal first.
Okay, I'll put some points
into Defense Support 1 first.
No noticeable changes...
Maybe once I'm in a party
I'll know for sure
whether I picked wrong
or if things will work out.
I'm Leila.
Assistant manager of
the Mercenary Office.
Um... I'd like to use these tickets.
I can give you a demi-human for those.
I'd prefer a vanguard. One who
can use a shield, if possible.
Mm.
All we've got left is a female Lizardman.
Lizardman?
She's a Rogue.
She can use most equipment
to some degree,
and she wears a leather buckler.
She should be plenty useful on the
first floor, the Field of Dawn, up ahead.
I see.
I guess I should start by testing out
Defense Support 1 on some weak monsters.
All right, I'd like to hire
this Lizardman, please.
Mm.
A Lizardman, huh?
So... something like this?
Sorry for the wait.
Huh?
Huh?!
THE WORLD'S STRONGEST REARGUARD
Rearguard is a job I'll
guard close to my heart.
THE WORLD'S STRONGEST REARGUARD
Uh... hello?
Her name's Theresia.
A... human girl?
Former human, to be exact.
Huh?
A demi-human is what a human
transforms into after being
killed by a monster in a labyrinth.
That's part of why they say the dead
can't be revived in Labyrinth Country.
If this transformation can be undone,
they can return to their original form.
But you treat her as a Lizardman now?
Well, it's not illegal to put
the slave crest on demi-humans.
We can't communicate with them.
In general, they can only act
on the orders we give them.
Though they do fight instinctively
when combat breaks out.
I definitely didn't see this coming.
Well, my name is Arihito.
Nice to meet you, Theresia.
Well, I have a weapon now.
I'm finally starting to
look like a Seeker...
but I feel bad making a little
girl like this fight.
I'll find some weak monsters
to test my skills on,
then call it an early day.
So that's the first
labyrinth, Field of Dawn.
Oh, another novice, huh?
He's Japanese, just like the Valkyrie
in that last party we saw.
Oh, yeah, that hottie.
A Japanese Valkyrie?
That must be Chief Igarashi.
I guess she formed a party quick.
I'm Ribault.
I make a living finding
people in labyrinths
who can't move anymore and rescuing them.
H-Hello. My name is Arihito.
It's nice to meet you.
Um, Ribault-san...
Since you rescue people, does that mean
it's dangerous inside labyrinths?
Not really, as long as you don't
take on enemies you can't handle.
You have a mercenary with you,
so if you stick to low-level monsters,
you'll make it out on your own
as long as you're careful.
Just...
watch out for Named monsters.
Named monsters?
Any novice who takes on one
of those is gonna die.
If you see one, run straight outta there.
They die?
Understood. Thank you for
that important lesson.
There are other parties in there, too,
and if you're in a pinch, just call us.
We patrol regularly, but we can't
be in there around the clock.
Got it.
Right...
Theresia.
Let's go.
Is that fluffball a monster?
ENCOUNTERED MONSTER: COTTON BALL
LV. 1 — DROPS: ??? — CAUTION
Cotton Ball, level 1...
Is this one of the monsters
Ribault talked about?
You're kidding me...
It hits that hard at level 1?
Let's run from this one, Theresia!
Theresia?!
Her life itself is being whittled down!
Wai—
What am I doing, letting a little
girl like her protect me?
I have to do something... but
what can I do as a Rearguard?
DEFENSE SUPPORT LV. 1: REDUCES INJURY
TO PARTY MEMBERS IN FRONT BY 10 POINTS
Defense Support... That's it!
Theresia, I'll back you up!
DEFENSE SUPPORT LV. 1
Okay, Theresia!
Make your move after I shoot it!
D-Did we beat it?
I should have used my
skill right at the start.
Are you okay with those wounds?
Should we exit for now and heal up?
I'm sorry, Theresia.
To be honest, I wasn't
taking this seriously.
Dying in a fight like this
wasn't even on my radar.
I finally understand now.
Thanks for protecting me.
From now on, I'll do my
part to protect you, too.
What's that?!
Chief Igarashi?
Is her party fighting something?
A Redface...
Damn it! Why is a Named monster here?!
Named?
BOOMERANG DIVE
Chief Igarashi!